bagtobrag.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy policy of BagToBrag — Bag to brag

PICVPIC LTD, (hereafter “PICVPIC”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) has developed this Privacy (“Policy”) in a continued effort to protect the privacy of our users. This policy applies to your use of our website and any related services (the “Website”) under the domain BagToBrag.com. By using or visiting the Website you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Website.

**Information Collected By Us**

Information submitted by a User

  * BagToBrag collects personal information when you register or request information from us. The personal information we collect is listed below: 
    * Email Address
    * First name
    * Last name
    * Gender
    * Avatar image

You may change your personal information by signing in to your BagToBrag account and selecting “Settings”.

  * Non-submitted Information Collected 
    * The website may also collect non-personal information not associated with your identity. We collect this data to improve the Website. The non-submitted information we collect is listed below: 
      * IP
      * Time
      * File
      * Data Transferred
      * Browser type and version
      * Operating System

PICVPIC follows the guidelines established by the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). Therefore, we will never knowingly accept or solicit personally identifiable information from a user known to be under the age of (13). If you have a concern, please refer to our Terms of Service for information on how to notify us.

**Use of Cookies**

  * This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for website's to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer / device.
  * Cookies are small files saved to the users computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the users interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.
  * Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.
  * Other cookies may be stored on your computer’s hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected

**Contact & Communication**

  * Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
  * This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
  * We will not sell or rent Your personal information to others, except to the extent necessary to fulfil any requests by You to share content through another Website or partner.
  * Your email may be used to answer any requests made by you, or to provide status updates around the Website or its processes.
  * PICVPIC may combine Your information with other information about You that PICVPIC receives from other sources.
  * We may aggregate data (gather up data from across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertise and otter third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

**Email Newsletter**

  * This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.
  * Subscriptions are taken in compliance with UK Spam Laws detailed in the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter program. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the business address at the bottom of this policy.
  * Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a comprehensive list].
  * This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.
  * In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign. If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to un-subscribe will by detailed instead.

**External Links**

  * Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.
  * The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Adverts and Sponsored Links**

  * This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.
  * Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computer’s hard drive. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Social Media Platforms**

  * Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.
  * Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. Neither this website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.
  * This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account

**Data Security**

  * We take a reasonable effort to protect your personal information stored in our database. Access to your personal information is limited to our authorised staff who need that information to perform their job function.

**Legal Disclaimer Disclosure**

  * We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Website.
  * PICVPIC reserves the right to change or modify the Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the modified Policy on the Website. Your continued use of the Website indicates your acceptance of any revised Policy.

**Notice of Change**

  * PICVPIC may provide you with notifications that include, without limitation, any changes at are made to the Policy or other Website related service, by postings on the Website or via email to a user.
